[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "What can we do about it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "can", "we", "do", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "Well, first of all, it's very dangerous to try to preventively detain people based on predictions of what they're liking to do in the future.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "it", "'s", "very", "dangerous", "to", "try", "to", "preventively", "detain", "people", "based", "on", "predictions", "of", "what", "they", "'re", "liking", "to", "do", "in", "the", "future", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "Because as there are more of them, the need to do something becomes more and more urgent, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "as", "there", "are", "more", "of", "them", ",", "the", "need", "to", "do", "something", "becomes", "more", "and", "more", "urgent", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "RBR", "CC", "RBR", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "I think that's exactly right.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "'s", "exactly", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "''", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "Dan Baum, how do you make it harder for crazy people to legally buy weapons that they can go and do crazy things with?", "question_tokens": ["Dan", "Baum", ",", "how", "do", "you", "make", "it", "harder", "for", "crazy", "people", "to", "legally", "buy", "weapons", "that", "they", "can", "go", "and", "do", "crazy", "things", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "A ROAD TRIP\": The first thing you do is you do no harm.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "ROAD", "TRIP", "''", ":", "The", "first", "thing", "you", "do", "is", "you", "do", "no", "harm", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dan Baum"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "What do you do about that culture?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "do", "about", "that", "culture", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "Well, of course it doesn't mean what you just said.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "of", "course", "it", "does", "n't", "mean", "what", "you", "just", "said", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "JJ", "PRP", "RB", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "Can I respond to that?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "respond", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "Well, I mean -- let me just -- before we go to Alan, what I would say is, it's very good to have the debate.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", "--", "let", "me", "just", "--", "before", "we", "go", "to", "Alan", ",", "what", "I", "would", "say", "is", ",", "it", "'s", "very", "good", "to", "have", "the", "debate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "But this particular one of crazy people doing crazy things, what can you do to try and red flag these people?", "question_tokens": ["But", "this", "particular", "one", "of", "crazy", "people", "doing", "crazy", "things", ",", "what", "can", "you", "do", "to", "try", "and", "red", "flag", "these", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VBN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "Well, homicide, murder, is a byproduct of many different qualities.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "homicide", ",", "murder", ",", "is", "a", "byproduct", "of", "many", "different", "qualities", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "What do we do about that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "we", "do", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "Well, two things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "two", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "WP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Unless it is to do harm?", "question_tokens": ["Unless", "it", "is", "to", "do", "harm", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Mass shooting is an end point in an individual who may have mental illness and who may not.", "answer_tokens": ["Mass", "shooting", "is", "an", "end", "point", "in", "an", "individual", "who", "may", "have", "mental", "illness", "and", "who", "may", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "Final question, though, I mean, from all that you have seen, all the cases you've been involved in, and so on, do you think there is a coherent argument to just have tougher gun laws in America?", "question_tokens": ["Final", "question", ",", "though", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "from", "all", "that", "you", "have", "seen", ",", "all", "the", "cases", "you", "'ve", "been", "involved", "in", ",", "and", "so", "on", ",", "do", "you", "think", "there", "is", "a", "coherent", "argument", "to", "just", "have", "tougher", "gun", "laws", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "I don't agree.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "agree", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Why are you going all out then against President Obama over this?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "going", "all", "out", "then", "against", "President", "Obama", "over", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "RP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Well, it's actual fact.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "actual", "fact", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "Would you go along with that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "go", "along", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "Well, there's nothing wrong with flexibility.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "'s", "nothing", "wrong", "with", "flexibility", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "Ben Labolt?", "question_tokens": ["Ben", "Labolt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "Governor Romney in this letter would have undermined the work requirement.", "answer_tokens": ["Governor", "Romney", "in", "this", "letter", "would", "have", "undermined", "the", "work", "requirement", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben Labolt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney"]}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "It's got a certain ring to it, hasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "got", "a", "certain", "ring", "to", "it", ",", "has", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "I think I'd have to agree with Governor Romney when he called that Obama-loney.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "'d", "have", "to", "agree", "with", "Governor", "Romney", "when", "he", "called", "that", "Obama-loney", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "When a Great White Shark sinks its fangs into you, what does it feel like?", "question_tokens": ["When", "a", "Great", "White", "Shark", "sinks", "its", "fangs", "into", "you", ",", "what", "does", "it", "feel", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "Well, people ask me if I knew it was a shark.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "people", "ask", "me", "if", "I", "knew", "it", "was", "a", "shark", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Great White Shark"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "Why did you stay so cool?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "stay", "so", "cool", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "I think the most surprising thing to me about this whole incident is that I didn't actually feel afraid.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "most", "surprising", "thing", "to", "me", "about", "this", "whole", "incident", "is", "that", "I", "did", "n't", "actually", "feel", "afraid", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Was your son as phlegmatic about it all as you clearly were?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "your", "son", "as", "phlegmatic", "about", "it", "all", "as", "you", "clearly", "were", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "It's harder for me to know what was going through his mind.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "harder", "for", "me", "to", "know", "what", "was", "going", "through", "his", "mind", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "No, you wouldn't stick around to chat, would you?", "question_tokens": ["No", ",", "you", "would", "n't", "stick", "around", "to", "chat", ",", "would", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "TO", "VB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "No, no, no, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "no", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "Or is it simply that with the modern media phenomena, that when there is an attack like this, it gets such a huge play on the Twitter-verse, if you like, that it seems like there are a lot more?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "it", "simply", "that", "with", "the", "modern", "media", "phenomena", ",", "that", "when", "there", "is", "an", "attack", "like", "this", ",", "it", "gets", "such", "a", "huge", "play", "on", "the", "Twitter-verse", ",", "if", "you", "like", ",", "that", "it", "seems", "like", "there", "are", "a", "lot", "more", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "IN", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "People's fear of shark attacks -- and I spoke to a couple of folks today, and they said God, I would never get in the water.", "answer_tokens": ["People", "'s", "fear", "of", "shark", "attacks", "--", "and", "I", "spoke", "to", "a", "couple", "of", "folks", "today", ",", "and", "they", "said", "God", ",", "I", "would", "never", "get", "in", "the", "water", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "And if that is true, why do they keep gnawing it at?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "that", "is", "true", ",", "why", "do", "they", "keep", "gnawing", "it", "at", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "We speculate that that's the case.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "speculate", "that", "that", "'s", "the", "case", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "Why not?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "Chris, you say you were swimming back with your son.", "answer_tokens": ["Chris", ",", "you", "say", "you", "were", "swimming", "back", "with", "your", "son", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "When you actually got back to land, what was your reaction then?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "actually", "got", "back", "to", "land", ",", "what", "was", "your", "reaction", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "Euphoria.", "answer_tokens": ["Euphoria", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "Did you realize then the enormity of what you just survived?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "realize", "then", "the", "enormity", "of", "what", "you", "just", "survived", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "How is your leg?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "your", "leg", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "I'm walking around.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "walking", "around", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "Is winning an Olympic gold for you the absolute number one dream?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "winning", "an", "Olympic", "gold", "for", "you", "the", "absolute", "number", "one", "dream", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120807pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "CC", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 659, "question": "For all seven hours of the day, you're think of that gold medal, the podium, the American anthem?", "question_tokens": ["For", "all", "seven", "hours", "of", "the", "day", ",", "you", "'re", "think", "of", "that", "gold", "medal", ",", "the", "podium", ",", "the", "American", "anthem", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 660, "answer": "Yeah, definitely, especially in the car ride to and from gym.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "definitely", ",", "especially", "in", "the", "car", "ride", "to", "and", "from", "gym", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["seven hours of the day"]}}]